Excuse me, sir. Quick question for
you, man. Is this your G-Wagon?
Yeah, it is.
And what do you do for a living, man? How
are you able to afford a G-Wagon out in Houston, Texas?
I started a cybersecurity company.
What's been the most amount of money
that you've ever made in a single year?
$194 million.
$2.3 million.
$6 million.
$8 million.
And what happened that year that
you were able to make $8 million?
We sold our company.
How much did you sell your company for?
There were some contingencies. It was over $740 million.
Have you ever been broke before?
I spent the first half of my life broke.
My parents were divorced. I came
from nothing. My mom's car got repossessed.
I had a tough upbringing.
How old are you now?
I'm 27.
How old were you when you became a millionaire?
That was this year.
I knew I was going
to be successful no matter what.
Somebody once told me, if you
want to go fast, go by yourself.
But if you want to
go farther, go with people together.
And any last words of advice to the younger generation?
Inspire them to own a Lamborghini one day, man.
This is a lot of people's dream car right here.
You want to make money, especially in the United States.
I wouldn't say entrepreneurship. You just got to go to...
Houston, Texas is the number eight city
in the entire world with the most millionaires.
And today...
We're going to be going all over
the wealthiest shopping district in all of Houston
to ask holiday shoppers the most amount of
money that they've ever made in a single year
and how you can start your
path to becoming wealthy going into 2024.
With that being said, let's
get this video on the way.
What industry did you decide to pursue a career in?
I'm in the investment
management business, wealth management.
And how long have you been in finance for?
40 years.
You were in finance for 40 years?
Yeah.
And what was the best financial...
Still am.
Still am?
Yeah.
What were your career...
What's been the best financial advice that you've ever received that you
pass on to the younger generation and kids coming out of school today?
Most people will sacrifice what they
want most for what they want now.
And now is the most
expensive word in the English language.
Wow.
You got to be able to
hang into things for the long haul.
And I know that you've been in
finance, but are you a business owner?
Well, yes, I have my own wealth
management firm that I started 13 years ago.
And it's about seven times the size of my brokerage
practice when I left the brokerage industry 13, 14 years ago.
What has been the most amount of money
that you've ever made in a single year?
$6 million.
Have you ever been broke before?
I spent the first half of my life broke.
And that's where I learned a lot of
really good lessons about what not to do.
My parents were divorced.
I came from nothing.
My mom's car got repossessed.
I had a tough upbringing.
Yeah.
Let me ask you this.
What was that turning point like for you, right?
For somebody who may be kind of at rock bottom
right now, maybe they're stuck in that cycle of poverty,
what is an actionable step that somebody can take
right now to get their life back on track?
I would say go to church, pray, learn, be curious, figure out
how things work, and learn how to articulate that to other people.
People will seek you out
if you're knowledgeable and trustworthy.
How old are you now?
I'm 64.
You look 40, though.
How old were you when you became a millionaire?
I was 36.
For a young 20-year-old kid watching this right now,
aspiring to become successful like yourself, give them the blueprint.
Like, how can somebody become a millionaire going into 2024?
Think about businesses that generate
recurring revenue that is non-transactional.
You can make a lot of money in commercial real estate,
but you've got to go out and find the next deal.
Finding deals is what makes it tough.
I played the long game.
My clients hire me on retainer, and they pay me.
Every year, that business is also super scalable because I can
deliver one set of transactions and apply it to 100 different people,
and those 100 people are paying me for that.
And so scalability is a really important part of businesses.
Thinking about how to mass-produce one little thing that you can deliver to lots of
people in a non-transactional method is really a good way to make a lot of money.
You know they don't teach that in school, right?
They generally don't.
Among yourself and the most highly successful people that you study and
know, what is that one trait that they all have in common?
I'm faithful to my wife, my family, my business.
And then I get all choked up.
Just stay focused and do the right thing.
You got amazing advice there.
Thank you so much, man.
My guy was in finance for over 40 years,
and he made over $6 million in a single year.
But that advice at the end hit different.
Recurring revenue is the way to go.
Just a few weeks ago, Wes Watson told me that the double
R of the headrest in a Rolls Royce stands for recurring revenue.
Build it.
You're hearing now over and over again, recurring revenue is the
way to go, and they simply don't teach that in school.
Only at the School of Hard Knocks. Let's go.
Let's go get this next one.
My man just pulled up in
the G-Wagon out here in Houston, Texas.
We're going to go up to the car and see what
this guy did to be able to afford a G-Wagon, man.
Let's see what he has to say.
Excuse me, sir.
Quick question for you, man.
Is this your G-Wagon?
Yeah, it is.
And what do you do for a living, man?
How are you able to afford
a G-Wagon out in Houston, Texas?
I started a cybersecurity company.
A cybersecurity company.
How much money is that business
going to generate you this year?
We're doing like seven figures a month.
Seven figures a month.
Now, we go all over the country just
asking business owners their advice to young entrepreneurs.
Can we ask you a
few questions outside of the car?
No, of course.
Let's do it.
Awesome.
How old are you now?
I'm 27.
Yes, sir.
How old were you when you became a millionaire?
Yeah.
So that was this year.
That was this year.
What keeps people broke in today's world?
Ignorance.
Yeah.
And ignorance is not a demon, by the way.
So I think for me, the way
that you can collapse time is knowledge, right?
So everywhere you feel like there's darkness, search
for all of the knowledge that is allocated
to getting you the results that
you seek and you should be fine.
Going into 2024, what is the best industry
that people should be looking to get into
right now?
I mean, I'm biased.
I would say cybersecurity.
Yeah, man.
I was born and bred in a neighborhood where
about 40% of its GDP, like hundreds of billions
of dollars.
So if you can be the kind of person
that goes into an organization and helps protect the
organization, I mean, it's pretty much inevitable.
You'll get the money you're looking for.
Have you ever been broke before?
Yeah, it was a couple years ago, man.
Like 72 months ago.
When you were there, man.
What was the turning point like when
you're like, Wow, I need to change?
To be honest, I think the best decision
that I ever made was I stopped making decisions
everywhere that I wanted to go.
Someone had already gone.
And so I just needed to find people
who are already gotten there to follow whatever it
is that they did.
Honestly.
Good things don't take time. You can take 10 years and collapse
it into one getting around the right person getting around the right knowledge
So we put up on my guy in the G wagon
in his cybersecurity company is doing over a million dollars a month
But what did he say is the
number one thing that's keeping people broke?
It's their ignorance at the end of the day
You got to be humble, but you
got to spend money to make money
And what did he say you have to buy knowledge?
There's so many resources out there at the end of
the day. We don't lack resources. You just like resourcefulness
Let's go get this next one. What industry did
you decide to pursue a career energy oil and gas?
And how long have you been in the business
for 35 years 35 years over these 35 years?
What has been the most amount of money
that you've ever made in a single year?
Eight million eight million and what happened that year that you were
able to make eight million dollars. That's incredible. Seriously. We sold our company
How much did you sell your company for there was
some contingencies? It was over 740 million up to 790 million
How old are you now? I'm 65 65.
How old were you when you became a millionaire?
It wasn't too long ago
It was only about five years ago if you
were to go back in time and have a comment
differently
I'd start
In banking why why would you start in
finance because what I did was I started in
Technical geophysics and geology, which is great, but you're
only gonna be working for somebody if you do that
But if you understand where the money is coming from
or who's got the money and how that all works
Then you can do a lot more things
and then you benefit personally but more from it
But you ultimately exited a company for nine figures a lot
of entrepreneurs. They'll have a great idea. They'll start the business
They struggle to scale what took
you from eight to nine figures?
What's the secret to that?
Progressive took a lot of risk worked our asses off
and
got in at the right
time in the early stages when
Mexico opened up and we were there and we took that risk
and drilled that first well and it came it was a big one
Any last words of advice to someone trying to become
a millionaire going into 2024? How can you ask off?
Yeah study talk to people. It's all
about people and work with good people
That's I've been working with this guy
for 15 years because I trust them
There's the ripple effects of you still
you throw a stone in the water
You may only think that it's hair but it has an effect
on other things and so our job is just to do one thing
We don't have to solve everything
But that one thing that you can do in
your life can impact a country impact an economy
Which I've done several times in my career incredible
man. That's amazing. Thank you so much for your time
My guys sold his last
business for over 700 million dollars
But what did he do?
He became an expert and played in the same
game for over 30 years in the energy business
And that's why he was able to have a nine-figure exit guy
gave an incredible interview and some great game to all the entrepreneurs out
There man, let's go get this next one
All right, you guys my god
just put up in the Lamborghini years
We got to go up and see what this
guy did to be able to afford a Lamborghini
Out here in Houston, let's
see what he has to say
Excuse me, sir. Quick question for you man. Is this your
Lamborghini? Yes, and what do you do for a living man?
How are you able to afford a Lamborghini
out in Houston, Texas? I own a solar company
What's the most amount of money that you've
ever made in a single year to pay me?
How did you scale from six to seven figures?
Somebody once told me if you
want to go fast go by yourself
But if you want to go
farther go with people together, you know
So you gotta have the right people like, you
know, like my company we have a VP, right?
We got sales marketing you got all this stuff
And I have a structure where all these guys
are gonna be able to call me they need something
But I can call them to see what what's happening
So I think what helped
me was being good with people
You really need to know how to put those people together and
take care of your people because if you take care of your people
They will take care of your business.
Have you ever been broke before? Oh
Yeah, I mean I come from this country called Honduras,
you know, and I want to scope with that shoes
I came to this country when I was 14 didn't speak the language
and I went to I went in sales and I think sales really
Make the big difference in my life
where it put me to a situation
I missed so many great people and you want to
make money especially the United States. I wouldn't say entrepreneurship
You just gotta go to Commission sells no questions that you
can be selling solar. There are so many products out there
But yes, I was struggling. I actually didn't know anything
about this because in my country we couldn't have it right?
But I knew I was gonna be successful no matter what but I'm
glad I came to the United States and I was able to do
Well financially work my butt off like I see invest in
myself and here we are now. How old are you now?
I'm
34 now 34 how old were
you when you became a millionaire?
27 and any last words of advice to the
younger generation aspiring to own a Lamborghini one day man
This is a lot of people's dream car right here.
I will say I'm not a social media guy, right?
I want to make money where
I can disappear. That's my goal
Do not let social media fool you because it's
one thing reality with the reality of social media
So do not get caught up on the online gurus per se
all these people that they want to teach you how to make money
Nowadays if you want to learn something,
I think you can go to YouTube
You can go to YouTube
You can go to Google I'm not making this
up even if I have a question about something
I'll go to a chop GB like I'll ask so now
we have so much free data that you don't really need a
Guru, but you might need a mentor, right?
So do not let yourself fall into that
I must fear because it will cut you up and you'll get
into a rat race and trying to beat that when you could probably
Get it faster
If you had to the root of being generally
with yourself work your butt off and just keep going
So we put up on my guy in the
Lamborghini and he built a multi-million dollar business in solar
But he didn't start here. In fact, he started broken was an immigrant
from Honduras, but he invested in himself and he learned how to sell
What did he say some of the
most successful people there in high commission sales?
They may not even be running businesses, but they
know how to sell if you know how to sell
He will never go broke in business great
interview man. Let's go get this next one
What industry did you decide to pursue a
career in the lumber industry the lumber industry?
I know you're a business owner
Yes, what has been the most amount of money
that you've ever made in a single year in?
2022 my company did 194 million 194 million a lot
of entrepreneurs to have a great idea. They'll start the business
They don't know how to scale. What's the number one
thing that took you from eight to nine figures identifying people?
There's probably more I'm not in the lumber business.
I'm in the people business. So I'm hiring people
I don't believe in hiring somebody to do my
job and I view my job as running the company
But when you start getting a certain level you
do have to start considering letting go of certain things
You know the the business owner can't be
worried about the price of the toilet paper
How old are you now?
54 and how old were
you when you became a millionaire?
35 for a young 20 year kid watching this right now
aspiring to become successful like yourself give them the blueprint to become
A nine-figure entrepreneur ideas are cheap execution is everything break that
down. What's the importance of taking action? It's not just taking action
It's how you execute the follow-through. It's the
precision. It's the focus. Everybody has great ideas
There's not a lot of original thought but there's people that
execute things well, so I would say that's in a business perspective
That's good advice. Thank you so much
I appreciate this video was insane you
guys Houston had all the big dogs out
But we've got lots of amazing
content like this coming very soon
So be sure to LIKE
and subscribe for this amazing content
and
Click here to watch our full video going all over Miami asking
multi millionaires how you can start your path to becoming financially free going
into 2024